You're still spouting that
nonsense, you wretched brat?!
King of the Pirates?!
His attack actually hurt me?
So that's the haki that
the old man from Wano taught him...
What the hell was that haki?
Punches can hurt Kaido?!
We could actually pull this off!
More importantly, there's something
I have to tell Straw Hat...
Hey, punk!
Do you have any idea what it takes
to be King of the Pirates?!
What happened after I crushed him in Kuri?
Only a few people...
have ever gone toe to toe with me.
You... Do you really think
you're on their level?
Straw Hat!
Thunder Bagua!
Dammit!
I saw his attack coming,
but it was still too fast!
Well done!
You didn't take it head-on this time!
You suck at this, Kaido!
Trash should be burned!
Prometheus!
Yes, Mama!
Let's burn them to ashes!
Heavenly Feuer!
Foxfire Style: Flame-Rend!
Prometheus!
Kin'emon's technique!
That was awesome, Zoro!
I stole it!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
That hurt.
Don't lower your guard for a second, Luffy!
These are two Emperors we're dealing with!
Shambles!
Hey, Straw Hat.
Traffy!
You saved me! Thanks!
Listen!
Let's get one thing straight!
Huh?
I...
was already planning
on moving them downstairs!
Huh?!
But then you said...
Traffy!
Send all of them downstairs!
It sounded like...
I was following your order!
Huh?!
Who cares about that?!
Trafalgar...
I thought you'd finally become
Straw Hat's lackey...
N-No way!
Not that I care which of you losers
answers to the other...
– Huh?!
You're one to talk, loser!
Who are you calling "loser"?!
Quit your yapping!
– Huh?!
Incinerate them all, Prometheus!
Yes, Mama!
Heavenly Bon-Bons!
Okay, here's the deal!
– Huh?!
The first one to dodge her attack is a loser!
No way, you idiot!
You always wanna play some stupid game!
That's why you chumps
will never be big shots!
Fine then!
I guess you guys are losers!
– Huh?!
Suit yourselves!
Whatever!
Why don't you run, you chickenshits?!
Just dodge, you wimps!
Hey, watch out!
What are you guys doing?!
Now who's gonna become
the King of the Pirates?!
Let's see...
How am I gonna kill you?
Linlin, stand aside!
I wanna see how strong they are.
Huh?
What's the point in that?
Stay out of my way, Kamazo the Reaper!
Nice laugh you've got there. Very distinct.
You'd be dead if I had
my Punishers on back then.
Zorojuro...
I doubt it.
Beheading Claws!
Three-Sword Style:
Purgatory Oni Giri!
Too shallow!
I'm impressed!
I've gotta unleash Enma's power a bit more!
Kaido!
We're finishing this all at once!
Gear Fourth!
Boundman!
Hell yeah!
Punk Rotten!
Room!
Takt!
These guys are damn near monsters!
Bring it!
Let's see if any of you
have what it takes to become...
the King of the Pirates!
Gum-Gum...
Kong Gun!
Ow...
That stings!
I know you've got some thick skin!
But I bet I can still crush you to death!
You asked for it!
I'll show you how strong I am!
Punk Vise!
Not bad... but you'll need
more mass than that.
Allow me to add some, then.
What the...?!
Takt!
Damn!
You bastard!
Were you trying to kill me too?!
Oh, that hurts!
You're killing me!
Pain like this...
really takes me back!
Yum-yum!
I'm fully charged!
Nice try, you little shits...
I expect nothing less from idiots
who dream of being King of the Pirates...
But...
playtime is over!
What a shame...
None of you will last long at this point...
And once you all die, I'll take everything...!
Including each and every one of
your crew who followed you here!
There's no way I'll let that happen!
And we won't stop there!
We're taking your treasure too!
The poneglyphs.
I bet you guys brought some along, right?
I can't wait!
You won't feel that way
when I take your crew and treasure!
Whoever wins this battle
will be one big step closer...
to becoming King of the Pirates!
I'm the one who'll become...
the King of the Pirates!
Demolition Gust!
Kid!
It was a heap of scrap anyway!
Kaido!
You childish Pirate-King wannabes!
Entertain me!
Wano is mine to rule!
Would you carry...
Wano upon your back?!
Gum-Gum...
Kong...
Rifle!
Wake up, Mr. Emperor!
Slam Gibson!
Room!
Shambles!
I've never seen an anatomical
diagram of a dragon...
but I'm guessing your heart
is right about here!
Gamma Knife!
I'll destroy you from within!
How annoying!
So you've realized how tough my body is!
Looks like there's more
to you idiots than guts alone!
These hard scales have been
a huge pain in the ass!
How about I just cut into the body?!
Scyther...
Sonic!
That did some damage, didn't it?!
Kaido!
Indra!
Killer!
As long as you're under the open sky,
you have nowhere to run!
They're more entertaining than I expected!
Rhino Schneider!
Good one!
Traffy!
Get me up there!
Now you're telling me what to do...
I'm not your servant! I don't answer to you!
Foxfire Style...
Blast Breath!
...Flame-Rend!
Zoro!
One more time!
Traffy!
Huh?!
I told you to stop using me as a tool!
What the...?!
Look out, Kaido!
That's no ordinary sword!
One-Sword Style:
Flying Dragon Blaze!
Why do I feel...
Oden's presence in his sword?!
Dammit!
I missed!
You seem to have underestimated us.
Indra!
Zoro!
You've got no place to run!
God of Lightning Tenjin!
Dammit!
A natural disaster, huh?!
Straw Hat!
Why didn't the lightning hurt you?!
Because I'm rubber!
You're gonna pay for hurting
Zoro and the others!
Blast Breath!
My flames didn't work either?! Why?!
Guts!
Gum-Gum...
Kong...
Gatling!